Guide to the Junior League of Brooklyn records ARC.304
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 1: Administrative Records, 1910-2002; 21433
  Consists of administrative records created by the Junior League of Brooklyn. These materials include annual reports, the constitution and by-laws, position statements, goals and objectives, correspondence pertaining to administrative matters, officer and committee job descriptions, board and president's manuals, and general office administrative materials. Membership information is also included. Member files are arranged in alphabetical order by surname. They range in date from the 1930s to 2003. These files include members' admission applications, correspondence, resignation notices, transfer cards denoting members' moves to and from other leagues, and volunteer placement information. There is a flat box containing an oversized master membership list. This series also includes index cards with similar membership information in alphabetical order. Items in this series are in poor to excellent condition.
  - Constitution and by-laws, undated; 21434 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - By-laws changes and revisions, 1970-1987; 21435 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - By-laws changes and revisions, 1988-1990; 21436 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - By-laws changes and revisions, 1991-2000; 21437 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual reports, 1933-1936; 21438 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual reports, 1976-1979, 1986-1987; 21439 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual report and handbook, 1992-1993; 21440 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual reports (bound), 1913-1935; 21441 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual reports (bound), 1933-1946; 21442 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual reports (bound), 1947-1956; 21443 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports (bound), 1957-1967; 21444 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual reports (bound), 1967-1980; 21445 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports (bound), 1980-1983; 21446 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual reports-Committee and Task Force Submissions, 1973-1981; 21447 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Annual reports-Committee and Task Force Submissions, 1983; 21448 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Notes on annual reports 1913-1982, 1985; 21449 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Annual report form, 1981; 21450 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Goals and objectives, 1975-1996; 21451 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Position statements, 1976-1993; 21452 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Statement of purpose, 1979; 21453 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Elections, 1910-2002; 21454 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Absentee ballots for general meeting voting (Mar. 20), 1996; 21455 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board orientation, 1977-1980; 21456 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board manual, circa 1980; 21457 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board manual, 1983-1984; 21459 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board manual, 1987-1988; 21460 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board manual, 1989-1990; 21461 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board manual, 1990-1991, 1993; 21462 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board manual, 2001-2002; 21463 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Board member and committee job descriptions, 1980-1988; 21464 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Board member and committee job descriptions, 1990-1991; 21465 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Board members directory, 1990-1999; 21466 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Board structure, 1974-1986, 1989-1990; 21467 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Board training, 1993-1994, 1998; 21468 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - President's manual, 1978; 21469 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - List of officers and board of directors, 1910-1934, 1989-1994; 21470 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - JLB Representatives on community boards, 1978-1982; 21471 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Board nametags, 1910-2002; 21472 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Corresponding secretary, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 4, digital files)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Donated on one 3.5 inch floppy disk. The disk could not be successfully imaged.
    Conditions Governing Access
    This item is not currently available to researchers.
  - Corresponding secretary's guidelines, 1998-1999; 21473 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Corresponding secretary's reports, 1981-1998; 21474 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Council system, 1987, 1998; 21475 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Non-profit organizational conduct and strategy materials, 1977-2000; 21476 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Administrative assistant for Junior League of Brooklyn, 1988-1993; 21477 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Administrative assistant: Resumes and tests, 1988; 21478 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Administrative assistant: Job description, 1982-1986; 21479 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Administrative assistant: Personnel Info, 1984-1991; 21480 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Employee forms, 1980-1991; 21481 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Employee advertisements, 1983; 21482 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Legal assistance, 1983; 21483 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Calendar of member events, 1980-2000; 21484 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Office space: History and research, 1913-1982, 1975-1984; 21485 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 55 Pierrepont Street, 1982-1984; 21486 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 76 Montague Street, 1953-1976; 21487 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Meeting spaces, 1982-1985; 21488 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Meetings: Miscellaneous, 1992; 21489 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Caterers, 1984; 21490 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn location maps, 1910-2002; 21491 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Office procedures and forms, 1988-1991; 21492 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Records retention, 1981; 21493 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Safe deposit box, 1984-1985; 21494 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Office equipment: Addressograph, 1981-1985; 21495 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Office equipment: Gestetner Copier, 1984-1992; 21496 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Office equipment: IBM Selectric II, 1984-1992; 21497 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Office equipment: Miscellaneous, 1983-1992; 21498 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bulk mail information (1), 1982-1988; 21499 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bulk mail information (2), 1982-1988; 21500 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bulk mail information, 1989; 21501 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1975; 21502 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1984; 21503 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1985; 21504 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1988; 21505 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990; 21506 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1991; 21507 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1992; 21508 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1993; 21509 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1994; 21510 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1995; 21511 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2000; 21512 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Junior League Brooklyn Database, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 4, digital files)
    Donated on one 3.5 inch floppy disk containing 6 files, including one Microsoft Access database. Digital ID arc_304_media_001.
    Access to digital materials is available onsite at the Othmer Library. Requests to access digital materials must be made at least 2 days in advance by emailing library@brooklynhistory.org.
  - Membership fees – AJLI, 1984-1985; 21513 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Membership classification study, 1976-1983; 21514 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Membership mailings and notices, 1930-1950; 21515 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Membership mailings and notices, 1976-1977; 21516 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Membership mailings and notices, 1989-1996; 21517 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Membership mailings and notices, 1997-2000; 21518 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Membership statistics, 1979-1980; 21519 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Membership directories, 1961-1970; 21520 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Membership directories, 1971-1976; 21521 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Membership directories, 1977-1982; 21522 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Membership master list (oversized), 1989-1998; 21523 (Box 42, Folder -)
  - Member files – surname Acinapuro to Anderson, 1939-1999; 21524 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Member files – surname Ankerson to Ayers, 1931-2000; 21525 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Member files – surname Babcock to Barber, 1944-1985; 21526 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Member files – surname Barenblat to Batchelder, 1954-1992; 21527 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Member files – surname Beach to Beim, 1942-1996; 21528 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Member files – surname Bell to Beyer, 1940-2000; 21529 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Member files – surname Bhavnani to Bode, 1939-1999; 21530 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Member files – surname Bodkin to Boyer, 1935-2001; 21531 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Member files – surname Brady to Brown, 1937-1999; 21532 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Member files – surname Bruchhausen to Bryant, 1940-1998; 21533 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Member files – surname Buck to Bynane, 1946-1999; 21534 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Member files – surname Cain to Carpenter, 1941-1994; 21535 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Member files – surname Carr to Church, 1939-1999; 21536 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Member files – surname Clarke to Conway, 1952-2001; 21537 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Member files – surname Cook to Czerny, 1944-1998; 21538 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Member files – surname Dachs to Davis, 1950-1993; 21539 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Member files – surname Deacon to Deysson, 1947-1997; 21540 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Member files – surname Dickey to Downie, 1940-1997; 21541 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Member files – surname Doyle to Durkin, 1939-2001; 21542 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Member files – surname Eager to Ewing, 1941-2002; 21543 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Member files – surname Fabricand to Ferris, 1941-1999; 21544 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Member files – surname Ferry to Fitzpatrick, 1940-1993; 21545 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Member files – surname Flaster to Fowler, 1941-1994; 21546 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Member files – surname Francis to Fuqua, 1939-1991; 21547 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Member files – surname Gallagher to Gehshan, 1942-2001; 21548 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Member files – surname Ghatlas to Glenn, 1942-1998; 21549 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Member files – surname Goetz to Grant, 1938-1993; 21550 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Member files – surname Grassi to Guthrie, 1942-2001; 21551 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Member files – surname Habers to Hansom, 1939-1994; 21552 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Member files – surname Harding to Hazen, 1936-1997; 21553 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Member files – surname Healy to Hettich, 1943-1998; 21554 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Member files – surname Hilton to Hoffman, 1939-1997; 21555 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Member files – surname Holden to Hume, 1934-1999; 21556 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Member files – surname Hummer Huyck, 1952-1991; 21557 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Member files – surname Idler to Iuse, 1938-2000; 21558 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Member files – surname Jack to Johnson, 1939-2000; 21559 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Member files – surname Johnston to Jupp, 1961-2001; 21560 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Member files – surname Kalnins to Kelly, 1953-1999; 21561 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Member files – surname Kennedy to Keyes, 1938-1991; 21562 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Member files – surname Kilbane to Knowles, 1947-2001; 21563 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Member files – surname Koehler to Kwong, 1947-1999; 21564 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Member files – surname Lack to Lappner, 1938-2001; 21565 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Member files – surname Lee to Lewis, 1938-1999; 21566 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Member files – surname Lichenstein to Love, 1939-1998; 21567 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Member files – surname Lovell to Lynd, 1938-1994; 21568 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Member files – surname Macari to Martin, 1948-2001; 21569 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Member files – surname Martineau to Maynard, 1942-1998; 21570 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Member files – surname McAllister to McFayden, 1939-1998; 21571 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Member files – surname McGrath to McVie, 1948-1997; 21572 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Member files – surname Meade to Myers, 1940-1997; 21573 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Member files – surname Michell to Mitchell, 1942-2003; 21574 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Member files – surname Mobilia to Moser, 1937-1994; 21575 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Member files – surname Moses to Mysliwiec, 1950-2001; 21576 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Member files – surname Nash to Newhouse, 1941-1998; 21577 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Member files – surname Nichols to Nunez, 1968-1999; 21578 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Member files – surname Odell to Owens, 1940-1999; 21579 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Member files – surname Paar to Pemberton, 1938-2002; 21580 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Member files – surname Peper to Petschek, 1941-1994; 21581 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Member files – surname Phelan to Powers, 1938-2002; 21582 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Member files – surname Pratt to Pyle, 1941-1991; 21583 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Member files – surname Quattlebaum to Quinn, 1970-2002; 21584 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Member files – surname Rae to Roberts, 1941-1997; 21585 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Member files – surname Robertson to Rowe, 1939-1994; 21586 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Member files – surname Rubin to Ryan, 1939-1995; 21587 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Member files – surname Sabatine to Schmerge, 1940-1994; 21588 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Member files – surname Schoch to Scully, 1942-1993; 21589 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Member files – surname Seidel to Shell, 1933-1993; 21590 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Member files – surname Shellenberger to Shufeldt, 1943-1995; 21591 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Member files – surname Silver to Sommerkamp, 1938-1994; 21592 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Member files – surname Spain to Stockmar, 1940-1997; 21593 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Member files – surname Stokes to Szapiro, 1941-1991; 21594 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Member files – surname Taaffe to Thomson, 1938-2000; 21595 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Member files – surname Thornbury to Tweedy, 1941-1991; 21596 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Member files – surname Ubelli to Van Pottelbergh, 1943-1999; 21597 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Member files – surname Van Wagoner to Vreeland, 1948-2003; 21598 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Member files – surname Wade to Weaver, 1938-1993; 21599 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Member files – surname Webb to Whitehead, 1944-1997; 21600 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Member files – surname Wiitalia to Winterer, 1939-1995; 21601 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Member files – surname Winterrowd to Wunder, 1939-1997; 21602 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Member files – surname Yglesias to Zumpano, 1938-2000; 21603 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Member index cards – surname Abberley to Greason, 1910-circa1980; 21604 (Box 27, Box-file A)
  - Member index cards – surname Green – Owens, 1910-circa1980; 21605 (Box 27, Box-file B)
  - Member index cards – surname Palmer – Zumft, 1910-circa1980; 21606 (Box 27, Box-file C)
- Series 2: Meetings and Minutes, 1910-2001; 21607
  Holds records of the monthly meetings of the Junior League of Brooklyn's executive board, the group's general meetings held for all members, and annual meetings. The series includes minutes and related materials such as agendas, committee and task force reports, and other handouts. The meeting minutes detail which officers were present, who presided over the meeting, and when it was called to order and adjourned. Topics in the minutes cover all organizational matters such as development, project and volunteer placement, committee and task force updates, and membership status. Both board meeting minutes and general meeting minutes are arranged in chronological order beginning from the oldest records to the most recent. Certain annual, opening and closing meeting minutes are in separate folders based on original order, also arranged chronologically. Items in this series are in poor to very good condition.
  - Board meeting minutes book, 1911-1922; 21608 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes (May 1914-May 1924), 1914-1924; 21609 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes (Oct. 1924-May 1929), 1924-1929; 21610 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes (Oct. 1929-Oct. 1931), 1929-1931; 21611 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes (Nov. 1931-Sept. 1934), 1931-1934; 21612 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes (Oct. 1934-Apr. 1937), 1934-1937; 21613 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes (Sept. 1937-Apr. 1939), 1937-1939; 21614 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes (May 1939-Dec. 1940), 1939-1940; 21615 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1941; 21616 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-Apr.), 1942; 21617 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes (May 1942-Dec. 1943), 1942-1943; 21618 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan. 1944-Dec. 1945), 1944-1945; 21619 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan. 1946-Dec. 1947), 1946-1947; 21620 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan. 1948-Dec. 1949), 1948-1949; 21621 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1950; 21622 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1951; 21623 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1952; 21624 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1953; 21625 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1954; 21626 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1955; 21627 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1956; 21628 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-Nov.), 1957; 21629 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1958; 21630 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-Apr.), 1959; 21631 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1960-1962; 21632 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1963-1964; 21633 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1965-1967; 21634 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1968-1971; 21635 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1972-1973; 21654 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1974-1975; 21655 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1976; 21656 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1977; 21657 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1978; 21658 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1979; 21659 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1980; 21660 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1981; 21661 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1982; 21662 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-July), 1983; 21664 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes (Aug.-Dec.), 1983; 21666 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-June), 1984; 21667 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes (Aug.-Dec.), 21668 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1985; 21669 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes (1), 1986; 21670 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes (2), 1986; 21671 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1987; 21672 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-July), 1988; 21673 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting minutes (Aug.-Dec.), 1988; 21674 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-March), 1989; 21675 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Board meeting minutes (April-July), 1989; 21676 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Board meeting minutes (Aug.-Dec.), 1989; 21677 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-May), 1990; 21678 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Board meeting minutes (June-Dec.), 1990; 21679 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1991; 21680 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1992; 21681 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-June), 1993; 21682 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Board meeting minutes (July-Dec.), 1993; 21683 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan-May), 1994; 21684 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Board meeting minutes (June-Dec.), 1994; 21685 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-May), 1995; 21686 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting minutes (June-Dec.), 1995; 21687 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-May), 1996; 21688 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Board meeting minutes (June-Dec.), 1996; 21689 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-May), 1997; 21690 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Board meeting minutes (June-Dec.), 1997; 21691 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-April), 1998; 21692 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Board meeting minutes (May-Dec.), 1998; 21693 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting minutes (Mar.-Sept.), 1999; 21694 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Board meeting minutes (Oct.-Dec.), 1999; 21695 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Board meeting minutes (Jan.-May), 2000; 21696 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Board meeting minutes (July-Dec.), 2000; 21697 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2001; 21698 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Executive committee meetings, 1958-1972; 21699 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Executive committee meetings, 1980-1982; 21700 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Executive committee meetings, 1983-1985; 21701 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Executive committee meetings, 1986-1987; 21702 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Executive committee meetings, 1988-1990; 21703 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Executive committee meetings, 1992-1999; 21704 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Annual meetings, 1954-1963; 21705 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Annual meetings, 1962-1976; 21706 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Annual meetings, 1978-1985; 21707 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Annual meetings, 1986-1987; 21708 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Annual meetings, 1988-1993; 21709 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Open meetings, 1976-1991, 1993; 21710 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Mid-year meetings, 1991-1998; 21711 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Closing meetings, 1987-1989; 21712 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Business meeting minutes, 1958-1967; 21713 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - General meeting minutes (1910-Nov. 1917), 1910-1917; 21714 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - General meeting minutes (Nov. 1917-May 1923), 1917-1923; 21715 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - General meeting minutes (Dec. 1923-May 1925), 1923-1925; 21716 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - General meeting minutes (Dec. 1925-May 1929), 1925-1929; 21717 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - General meeting minutes (Oct. 1929-May 1934), 1929-1934; 21718 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - General meeting minutes (Oct. 1934-Oct. 1935), 1934-1935; 21719 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - General meeting minutes (Nov. 1935-Apr. 1937), 1935-1937; 21720 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - General meeting minutes (May 1937-May 1938), 1937-1938; 21721 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - General meeting minutes (Oct. 1938-Mar. 1941), 1938-1941; 21722 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - General meeting minutes (Apr. 1941-Nov. 1942), 1941-1942; 21723 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - General meeting minutes (Feb. 1943-Oct. 1945), 1943-1945; 21724 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - General meeting minutes (Jan. 1946-Dec. 1949), 1946-1949; 21725 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - General meeting minutes (Jan. 1950-Mar. 1953), 1950-1953; 21726 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - General meeting minutes (May 1953-1964), 21727 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - General meeting minutes, 1976-1977; 21728 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - General meeting minutes, 1984-1985; 21729 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - General meeting minutes, 1996-1999; 21730 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Series 3: Accounting and Financial, 1941-2000; 21731
  The series consists of the Junior League of Brooklyn's financial records. These materials include financial status and budget reports, ledgers, and documents generated by the Finance Committee and the Treasurer. The records span from 1941 to 2000. The items are in fair to excellent condition.
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1977-1980; 21735 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1981-1982; 21736 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1983-1984; 21737 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1984-1985; 21738 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1985-1986; 21739 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1986-1987; 21740 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1988-1989; 21741 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1990-1991; 21742 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1992-1993; 21743 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1994-1995; 21744 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1996-1997; 21745 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1997-1998; 21746 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1998-1999; 21747 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Financial status and budget reports, 1999-2000; 21748 (Box 14, Folder 7)